**************************************
Android GoAdventure aka Project λ (?) TODO List
**************************************
-font for text
-find out how to and implement sound
-main menu design implementation (modulating photon, custom buttons, text, etc)
-pause menu design (buttons, background, etc)
-add trail to player and shrink size of player entity
-work on visual design for filters, blocks, prisms (for prisms, luis and nick were thinking of an equilateral triangle inside the 45-45-90 one to give a depth illusion
-make the player be able to die (return to main menu on death? restart game? other behavior?)
-add a game object generation algorithm (arrays of each object are already in place on initialization)
-decide on and implement prism collision behavior (rainbow split(?), etc)


//down the road, once other core gameplay elements are in place
-implement score counter (maybe scales w/ time(?))
-work on in game background (probably implemented later after actual game features are fleshed out so we can mimic it)



//test build things to look into
-crash on restart (consistently)
-fps counter (to identify anything that might cause a frame drop)